Guide to the History of Education Society collection, 1960-2013 MS2341
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Governance and Society records, 1960-2006; Series 2
  - Correspondence between John W. Tresch and History of Education Quarterly, 1984; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence between Joseph M. Stettar and Paul H. Mattingly, December 27, 1984; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence between K.A. Pickens and Ms. Roberta Wein, September 9, 1974; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence between K. de Clerk and Mr. Benson, November 14, 1978; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence between Keith Hoskin and Paul H. Mattingly, December 12, 1982; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence between Keith Hoskin and Paul H. Mattingly, February 9, 1983; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence between L. Glenn Smith and Educational Studies, November 23, 1981; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence between Laurence Veysey and Paul H. Mattingly, September 21, 1973; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence between Laurence Veysey and Paul H. Mattingly, October 24, 1971; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence between Laurence Veysey and Paul H. Mattingly, Undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence between Laurence Veysey and Paul H. Mattingly, April 14, 1969; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence between Laurence Veysey and Paul H. Mattingly, July 7, 1976; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence between Laurence Veysey and Paul H. Mattingly, April 19, 1976; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence between Laurence Veysey and Paul H. Mattingly, May 3, 1976; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - Board of Directors Agenda, 1979; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Casting Networks of Good Influence: Moral Education, April 9, 1981; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Corrections, Undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence between Alan Creutz and Paul Mattingly, 1975-1977; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Alumni Office School of Education, August 1, 1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Amy C. Schutt, June 5, 1989; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence between Ann Taylor Allen, Mr. Benson, June 14, 1982; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence with Berenice Fisher, 1971; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence with Bill Komodore, 1972; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence with Bill Komodore, August 3, 1973; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence between Bob Ruderman and Millard Clements, November 18, 1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence with Charles Komodore, 1973; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence with Chairman Standing Committee on Institutional Development Council, December 2, 1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence between David and Edward McClellan, February 13, 1987; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence with Dean Andrea Wilson, November 18, 1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence with Dr. Henry J. Perkinson, 1966; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence with Dr. Robert Fite, July 5, 1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence with Education Recording Office, November 15, 1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence with Ed, January 8, 1986; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence between Erwin V. Johanningmeier and Jennings L. Wagoner, October 24, 1984; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence with Ezri Atzmon, 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence with Ezri Atzmon, 1966; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence with Ezri Atzmon, 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence with Ezri Atzmon, 1972-1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence with F.W. Faxon company, August 19, 1971; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence with Gale Research company, February 25, 1973; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence between Geoffrey C. Fidler and Robin K. Berson, November 9, 1973; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence with Graduate Office, November 19, 1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence between H.L. Warm Schupf and Sir, December 14, 1971; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence from Harvey Neufeldt and Paul Mattingly, January 26, 1978; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence with Harold Silver, 1987-1988; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence with Henry J. Perkinson, 1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence with Henry J. Perkinson, 1971; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence with Henry J. Perkinson, 1966; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence with Henry J. Perkinson, 1970; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence with Henry J. Perkinson, 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence with Henry J. Perkinson, 1973-1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence with Henry J. Perkinson, 1968-1969; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence with History of Education Quarterly, 1976-1978; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence with History of Education Quarterly, May 30, 1973; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence with the Hyde Park Press, January 5, 1973; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence with Indiana University Northwest Division of Arts and Sciences, October 1, 1973; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence between the Internal Revenue Service and the History of Education Society, February 1, 1985; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence with the Jacques Cattell Press, November 28, 1973; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence from James A. Sokolow, April 15, 1977; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence between James Defibaush and Editor, August 12, 1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence between James J. Van Patten and Editor, December 2, 1971; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence between Jay Kaplan and the New York Council for the Humanities about Possible Participation as a Speaker, October 31, 1984; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence between Joel Perlman and Selma Berrol, David Ment, Maria Vinorskis, October 31, 1989; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence between John A. Andrew III and Editor, October 4, 1973; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence between John Whitehead and Jurgen Herbst, 1985; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence from Julia Wrigley, 1988-1989; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence with Jurgen Herbst, October 17, 1978; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence with Jurgen Herbst, 1978; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence with Jurgen Herbst, 1978-1982; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence between Jurgen and History of Education Society Board of Directors, October, 1979; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence between Laurence Veysey and Paul H. Mattingly, August 23, 1970; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence between Laurence Veysey and Paul H. Mattingly, February 10, 1970; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence between Laurence Veysey and Paul H. Mattingly, September 25, 1973; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence between Laurence Veysey and Paul H. Mattingly, October 17, 1973; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence with Lee A. Belford, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence with Lee A. Belford, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence with Lee A. Belford, 1971; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence with Lee A. Belford, 1972; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence with Lee A. Belford, 1973-1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence with Lee A. Belford, 1973; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence with Lee A. Belford, 1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence with Lee A. Belford, 1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence with Lee A. Belford, 1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence with Lee A. Belford, 1971-1972; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence with Lee A. Belford, 1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence with Lee A. Belford, 1973; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence with Lee A. Belford, 1973; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from Liesbeth Schrijvers, February 23, 1984; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence between Lloyd deMause and Paul Mattingly, 1972; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence between Lloyd G. Cooper and Henry J. Perkinson, March 12, 1968; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence between Louis Norton and Miss Ann Keppel, March, 1967; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence between Louise A. Tilly and Paul H. Mattingly, September 20, 1972; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence between Louise A. Tilly and Paul H. Mattingly, November 13, 1973; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence between Louise A. Tilly and Paul H. Mattingly, July 19, 1974; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence between Lucia Barbosa and History of Education Quarterly, 1984-1985; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence between Lucy Greaves and Mr. Robin Berson, 1980-1981; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence between Ludwig F. Schaefer and Paul H. Mattingly, June 18, 1974; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence between M. De Vroede and Edward McClellan, 1985; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence between Mandy Crozier and History of Education Quarterly, 1985; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence between Marcos Coeto and History of Education Quarterly, June 16, 1985; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence between Maria Augusta de Castro Correira and History of Education Quarterly, 1982; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence with Marie Patterson, 1973; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence with Marianne Komodore, 1972-1973; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence between Marianne Komodore and Bob and Ray, September 24, 1973; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence between Marianne Komodore and Gold Bond Stamp Company, August 1, 1972; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence between Marianne Komodore and Professor Francesco Cordasco, January 12, 1971; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence between Marilyn Tobias and Paul H. Mattingly, February 18, 1981; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence from Marilee Charboneau to Paul H. Mattingly, April 12, 1982; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence between Marjorie Pike and National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education Constituent Members, 1984; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence between Martha H. Verbrugge, Robin Berson, and Professor Rosenkranz, 1979-1980; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence between Mary Mangoid and Henry J. Perkinson, 1966; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence between Marvin Lazerson and Sol Cohen, October, 1982; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence between Maxine Seller and B. Edward McClellan, July 16, 1986; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence between Michael Frisch and Mr. Berson, May 25, 1982; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence between Michael J. Moore and Mr. Berson, March 21, 1983; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence between Michael Katz and Paul, 1984; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence between Melvin I. Urofsky and Henry J. Perkinson, 1967; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence between Members of History of Education Society and Carl Kaestle, May 12, 1981; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence between Members of History of Education Society and Harold Weschler, September 10, 1986; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence between Members of History of Education Society and Marvin Lazerson, 1981-1983; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence between Merle Borrowman and Paul H. Mattingly, 1973; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence between Merton J. Dillion and Henry J. Perkinson, 1967; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence from Michael Frisch to Paul Mattingly, February 25, 1979; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence between Michael G. Hall and Henry J. Perkinson, November, 1966; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence between Michael Kammen and Paul H. Mattingly, June, 1978; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence between Michael Kammen and Robin Berson, 1979; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence from Michael Lybarger to Robin K. Berson, September 13, 1984; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence from Michael Schudson to Robin Berson, July 19, 1982; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence of Michael W. Sedlak, November 7, 1980; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence between Michael W. Sedlak and Paul Mattingly, October 23, 1980; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence between Mindy Keiffer and History of Education Quarterly, April 23, 1985; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence from Morton J. Horwitz, Robin Berson, and James H. Keffner, 1978-1979; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence between Mr. Horowitz and Jennings Wagoner, June 19, 1984; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence to Mrs. Lila Rosenbaum, November 14, 1974; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence to Mrs. Mary Carey, 1966; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence to Mrs. Stella Kaisted, June 11, 1974; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence to Ms. Lynn Breger, July 3, 1973; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence between Mrs. Benson and Stanford University, 1982-1983; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence to Mrs. Lila Rosenbaum, November 11, 1974; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence with Murray S. Shereshewsky, 1972; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence between Murray S. Shereshwewsky and Malcolm Seeborn, February 1, 1972; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence with Murray S. Shereshewsky, 1970-1972; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence between Murray S. Shereshewsky and Silvio A. Bedini, September, 1971; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence between N. Ray Miner and David Minter, June 21, 1989; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence between N. Ray Hiner and Jurgen Herbst, June 20, 1989; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence with Nancy Green, 1985; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence between Neil Harris and Mr. Berson, January 21, 1980; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence between Nicholas V. Riasanovsky and William S. Reese, October 20, 1988; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence between the Nominating Committee and Members of History of Education Society, July, 1984; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence with Norma H. Thompson, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence with Norma H. Thompson, 1974; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence with Norma H. Thompson, 1974; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence with Norma H. Thompson, May, 1974; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence with Norma H. Thompson, 1973-1974; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence with Norma H. Thompson, 1973; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence with Norma H. Thompson, 1974; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence with Norma H. Thompson, 1973; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence with Norma H. Thompson, 1972; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence with Norma H. Thompson, 1971; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence with Norma H. Thompson, 1972-1973; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence with Norma H. Thompson, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Dr. Nicholas Piediscalzi, October 29, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Margaret Simko, November 27, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Mr. Bill Iverson, November 27, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Mr. David A. Ryan, October 30, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Mr. Paul Clark, October 29, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Mr. Richard J. Payne, October 29, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Ms. Della Smith, November 18, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Ms. Glenys, November 8, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Professor David A. Fee, November 8, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Professor Donald F. Williams, October 29, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Ron Chadwick, October 29, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Paul R. Clark, December 11, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Reverend Garland Pollard, October 22, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Reverend Herbert W. Chilstrom, November 8, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Reverend Howard L. Cassady, November 21, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Reverend Leonard Badia, November 25, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Reverend Lewis Bird, November 27, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Reverend Will C. Goodheer, November 14, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Reverence William Iverson, October 29, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence between Norman Lederer and Book Review Editor, November 14, 1978; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence between Norman Lederer and Paul Mattingly, March, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence between the Office and Mr. Murray Shereshewsky, March 26, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence between P.C. Wicks and Robin Berson, October 20, 1980; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence with Pace University, 1971, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence between Patricia Anne Carter and Editor, 1986; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence between Paul A. Gagnon and Mr. Berson, July 6, 1980; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence between Paul Kreise and Editor, October 5, 1977; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence with Paul H. Mattingly, 1969; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence with Paul Mattingly, 1979, 1983-1984; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence with Paul H. Mattingly, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence with Paul H. Mattingly, 1973-1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence with Paul H. Mattingly, June 19, 1970; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence with Paul H. Mattingly, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence with Paul H. Mattingly, 1971; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence with Paul H. Mattingly, 1972; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence with Paul H. Mattingly, 1972; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence with Paul H. Mattingly, June, 1978; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence between Paul Mattingly and Bill, June 23, 1969; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Board of Directors, 1979; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Bob, April 10, 1970; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Bob, December 2,1976; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence between Paul Mattingly and Carl Kaestle, October 27, 1981; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Carl Prince, February 16, 1983; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Dear Charles, November 14, 1969; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Dear Don, February 3, 1970; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Dr. Bullett, June 2, 1977; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Dr. Conway, November 11, 1982; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Dr. Buetow, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Dr. Lewis, February 18, 1975; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Edward R. Beauchamp, 1970; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Father Buetow, 1971; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Harrison, February, 1970; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and James C. McClelland, 1976; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Jim, September, 1970; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence between Paul Mattingly and Marvin Lazerson, July 21, 1983; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Mes Chers Collegues, October 31, 1980; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Mr. Handahu, 1975; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Mr. Hogeboom, 1975; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Mr. Looks, 1968, 1970; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Mr. Looks, 1975; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Mrs. Beach, June, 1971; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence with Pen Pal, September 27, 1972; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence between Norma H. Thompson and Professor A. Leroy Moore, November 8, 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence with Professor A. Stephen Higgins, November 15, 1972; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor Berlowitz, 1977; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor Bushman, February 20, 1969; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor Calabro, July 11, 1975; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor Calabro, December 27, 1976; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor Foster, January 24, 1970; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor Hareven, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor Hisham, May 30, 1969; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professors Leff, Kraditor, Stan, 1969-1971; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor McClelland, May 24, 1977; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence between Paul K. Mattingly and Professor Murphy, January 15, 1970; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor [Ronald Story], 1976; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 76)